vuoriclothing.com 2016-11-28

# Performance apparel with modern style | Vuori Clothing | Privacy Policy

This privacy statement provides notice of our information collection practices and of the ways in which your information may be used. This policy may change from time to time, so please check back periodically to review this information.

## Personally-Identifiable Information

Vuori Clothing typically receives specific data about its website visitors only when such information is provided voluntarily, such as when our visitors request information, purchase or enroll for services, provide resume information for employment opportunities, or send us e-mail. Of course, some of these activities require that you give us information, such as when you make a purchase, use a credit card to pay for services, submit your resume, or request certain types of information. When you provide personally-identifiable information to Vuori Clothing through one of our websites, it will be used to fulfill your specific request. In most cases, you will be given the opportunity to select whether you do, or do not, want Vuori Clothing to use this information for additional purposes. You may also request that Vuori Clothing not use your information by sending an e-mail to info@vuoriclothing.com, however, Vuori Clothing reserves the right, in its discretion, to send you bulletins and other important information about your Vuori Clothing services. Absent any instructions from you, Vuori Clothing may use information you provide to inform you about additional services and products offered by the Vuori Clothing family, authorized agents, and other goods and services providers with whom Vuori Clothing has relationships and whose offerings might be of interest to you. Vuori Clothing will not, however, sell or trade your personally-identifiable information unless we are authorized or legally required to do so, or in the case of imminent physical harm to the visitor or others. On those Vuori Clothing sites where you may provide Vuori Clothing with credit card or other ordering information via the web, Vuori Clothing protects and secures this information by employing commercially customary web-based security and encryption protocols, examples of which include Secure Socket Layer (SSL) and Secure Electronic Transaction (SET). On those sites where you voluntarily offer any feedback, data, answers, questions, comments, suggestions, ideas or the like, Vuori Clothing will treat that portion of the information as non-confidential and non-proprietary and, except as otherwise expressed in this privacy statement, Vuori Clothing assumes no obligation to protect such information from disclosure.

## Non Personally-Identifiable (Generic) Information

In general, Vuori Clothing gathers some generic information automatically. Generic information does NOT reveal the identity of the visitor. It usually includes information about the Internet address assigned to your computer, the number and frequency of visitors, and the Vuori Clothing sites visited. Vuori Clothing gathers this information for the limited purpose of determining customer service and website needs. We accomplish this by using certain technologies, including “cookies” (a technology that can be used to provide the visitor with tailored information about Vuori Clothing services). Vuori Clothing does not combine information collected in this way with any personally-identifiable information. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie and you can refuse it.

## Bulletin Boards and Third-Party Sites

Information that you disclose in a public space, including on any bulletin board or website Vuori Clothing may host is available to anyone else who visits that space. Vuori Clothing cannot safeguard any information you disclose in these locations. Additionally, Vuori Clothing websites contain links to sites that belong to third parties unrelated to Vuori Clothing. Vuori Clothing cannot protect any information you may disclose in these sites and recommends that you review the privacy policy statements of those sites you visit.

## Exceptions and Limitations

Notwithstanding the foregoing and in compliance with applicable laws, Vuori Clothing:

  1. cooperates fully with state, local, and federal officials in any investigation relating to any content (including personal or private electronic communications transmitted to Vuori Clothing) or purported unlawful activities of any user of the Service, and
  2. takes reasonable measures to protect its proprietary rights. For the limited purposes of accomplishing such cooperation and measures and in compliance with applicable laws, Vuori Clothing may be required to disclose personally identifiable information.

In addition, Vuori Clothing may elect to monitor the areas of communication of any kind:

  1. to satisfy any law, regulation, or government request;
  2. if such disclosure is necessary or appropriate to operate Vuori Clothing; or
  3. to protect the rights or property of Vuori Clothing or others.

In connection with the potential sale or transfer of any of its interest in www.Vuori Clothingcms.com, and other sites owned by the company, Vuori Clothing reserves the right to sell or transfer your information (including , but not limited to name, address information, and other information you provided to Vuori Clothing) to a third party that:

  1. concentrates its business in communication products or services;
  2. agrees to be Vuori Clothing’s successor in interest with regard to the maintenance and protection of information collected and maintained by Vuori Clothing; and
  3. agrees to the obligations of this policy statement
